

CONTACT

(300) 472-4553

davidcp22@gmail.com

Medellin, Antioquia

LENGUAGES

Spanish

English

PERSONAL SKILLS

Resilience

Leadership

Teamwork

DAVID STIVEN CASTAÑO PÉREZ

SYSTEMS ENGINEER

PROFILE

Systems engineer with skills in different areas of the industry such as software development and software engineering. I have worked as a Fullstack developer and I have handled technologies like C#, Entity framework, Unit Test, Azure, Angular, React, Kafka, Html5, CSS3, Git, SQL, SQL Server, Jenkins

WORK EXPERIENCE

Developer full stack / Perficient - PSL / Dec 2017 - present

Development of new functionalities and maintenance of web applications under the Scrum methodology., Web API in C# and front and Angular also technologies like Git Azure

University professor /Unisabaneta / Jan 2021 To Dec 2022

Teaching two class, one is software engineering and the other is neural networks

Developer full stack / Sinapsis / Sep 2016 To Dec 2017

Development of new functionalities and maintenance of web applications under the Scrum methodology. and technologies like Asp.Net, Web API in C# and front in Angular Js and Angular

EDUCATION

2024 MICROSOFT CERTIFIED: AZURE FUNDAMENTALS

2020 Certification Scrum Fundation Professional/ SFPC

2020 Systems Engineer

Universidad de Medellín

2015 Advanced English B1
Universidad de Medellín

2011 Academic BachelorI.E. Luis Lopez de Mesa

SKILLS



lar



Scrum



0

_ Re

